[insects chirping]
[in Burmese] Where did you get
the mohinga?
They made it at the center,
so I asked for some.
[slurps]
The guy taking us home said
we'll have to wait a few more days.
The police patrols are really strict,
so he can only bring the boat in
at certain times.
When I go out during the day,
make sure you lock the door.
It's a little salty, huh?
I miss Grandma's cooking.
Hang in there. Just a little longer,
and we'll be back with Grandma.
[bowl thuds]
[utensils clatter]
- [sobbing]
- [melancholic music playing]
[sobs]
[music darkens]
THE EVIL LAWYER
[music concludes]
[footsteps approaching]
DR. KORN SOPHONCHITRAK
[Pui] Hello, doctor.
Hello.
It's so bright in here.
Can I turn off the lights?
[dreamy intriguing music playing]
I like it in the dark.
Hmm…
How can I examine you
if the lights are off?
Well, if you don't want to examine me yet,
then I can examine you first.
Don't.
- [Pui smooches]
- [grunts]
[Pui moans]
Doctor…
- [Prangthip] Stop!
- [music stops]
What kind of story are you making up?
[echoing whoosh]
Our defense in court
will be that it was consensual.
You're going to make everyone think
my husband willingly slept with her?
Exactly. I told you
I didn't sleep with my patient.
None of it is true… you know that.
Find a different angle.
Even if my husband sleeps around,
that's a private matter between us.
But she has a transfer slip
for 50,000 baht from him,
which practically proves
he slept with her.
Just say she's blackmailing him.
My husband is just a gullible fool.
That's not a crime.
That's the plan.
If you can't do it, we're done.
With evidence this clear,
even I'm telling you it's impossible.
Do you think anyone else can do it?
Want to find out?
[soft tense music playing]
[Prangthip]
Don't be so confident, Attorney Jittri.
The only reason I hired you
is because my husband insisted.
I have many other ways to end this.
You're not the only way out of this.
We can't say it was consensual.
If word gets out
that I slept with a patient,
my career is over.
[Prangthip] Korn!
[music fades]
Damn! The doctor's wife
is fierce as hell.
I thought she was a damn warden.
So what's next, boss?
Do we fight or fold?
We can't back out now.
We still need a doctor
to testify in Mek's case.
Contact Tah's show.
We need to go big on this one.
[Kung in English] Yes, sir!
[in Thai] I won't miss a single detail.
What is it now?
Nothing.
Have you found the Burmese woman
you're looking for?
I found her brother,
but still no sign of her.
I told you. You'll never find her.
Why are you so sure I won't find her?
Because I've never seen anyone
who disappeared come back.
[dark pensive music playing]
[woman] Muleng, let go of me.
I have to go find Dad.
[girl] Dad is dead!
Do you hear me? Dad is dead!
- [fast thud]
- [sniffles]
He's still alive!
Muleng.
Muleng!
[music fades]
[Tah muffled] Attorney Jittri.
Attorney Jittri.
- [clearly] Attorney Jittri.
- Yes?
I can ask your client anything, right?
Go for it.
Okay, the audience is my witness.
I'm doing my job. I can ask anything.
They can't sue me later.
So, let's begin.
Dr. Korn.
With all due respect,
do you know what netizens
are calling you right now?
They're calling you…
Excuse my language, "the horny doctor."
So I'm going to ask you right here.
Let's talk man-to-man.
Confirm in front of everyone now
that you didn't do it.
I absolutely did not do it.
I've been a doctor for over 20 years.
I'd never throw my life away
over something like this.
That's understandable.
But there's one point everyone questions,
and it really is suspicious.
You transferred the money.
- [Korn] Mm-hmm.
- You can see why people would think
it was hush money.
Why else would you transfer it?
Well, when the patient came to see me,
she said she had back pain.
But based on my initial examination,
I thought the actual cause
might be a uterine tumor,
so I recommended
she get checked at the hospital.
But she said she had no money,
so I helped her out.
Do you know why many people
don't believe you?
Because you transferred a lot of money.
Isn't 50,000 a bit too much, doctor?
[guest] Not too much at all!
How is it too much?
Whoa, calm down, ma'am.
It's not your turn yet.
Camera, pan over here a bit.
Please introduce yourselves, ladies.
These are Dr. Korn's fans.
What are your names?
- Kanchana.
- [Tah] Kanchana.
Karuna.
- [Tah] Karuna.
- Yes.
Both are Dr. Korn's fans.
- You're his patients.
- Yes.
People in the area call him
Dr. Korn, The Angel's Touch.
One touch and you're cured, like that.
The doctor is highly skilled and kind.
He's taken care of us
for over ten years, right?
And no one has ever complained about him.
I think the person complaining,
- she's a real bitch.
- Ah, let's not--
No bad words, please.
We have a lot of kids watching at home.
I understand your frustration
since you both believe in Dr. Korn,
but the person who should be angrier,
or at least more upset
is probably this person.
Camera, pan over a bit.
This is…
Excuse me.
- Ms. Prangthip, Dr. Korn's wife, right?
- [Korn] Yes.
[Tah] Being supportive like this means
things are cleared up at home, right?
[Korn] All sorted out.
- [soft intriguing music playing]
- [indistinct chatter]
[Tah] Then let me ask you
another question.
Why do you think…
[Mek] On Facebook, people are supporting
the doctor and the victim equally.
But on TikTok,
the doctor is totally trending.
Why are we doing this to him?
It's totally useless in court.
[music fades]
Don't you get it?
It's called public condemnation, idiot.
Hmm.
Judges are still human.
They're bound to cave under pressure.
[tutting]
- [quirky music playing]
- [Tah speaking indistinctly]
I better keep my voice down, too.
Need to keep my voice down.
- [music concludes]
- If there are any remaining issues
or if there's anything else to discuss,
I'll see you in court.
Well, viewers, please use your discretion.
Listen to all sides,
and think about what incidents like this
can teach us.
Sometimes, to accuse someone,
you need sufficient evidence. Otherwise--
[cell phone ringing]
[Pui sniffles]
THE MOTHER POWER LAWYER
[dark somber music playing]
[Pui] Hello?
[lawyer speaking indistinctly over phone]
I didn't watch it.
I didn't watch it,
and I didn't read anything.
[lawyer] That's good.
And you deleted all the apps?
Yes, I deleted all the apps.
I did everything you told me to do.
[lawyer] Good job.
Don't worry about a thing.
We'll fight together.
I'm fully prepared for this.
I'll fight with everything I've got.
[lawyer] Okay. I'll come by tomorrow.
Let's rehearse one more time.
Yes.
[music fades]
[Pang] If we're talking about the East,
this place is in the top five.
The owner is Chaiwut.
People call him Chai.
He does it all.
Cold storage, transport,
and fishing boats.
When Seya and his sister
sneaked into Thailand,
the broker brought them here.
But Seya was separated
and sent to work on a boat.
Scammed workers get their IDs taken away
and are forced to work off their debt.
They could work themselves to death
and never pay it off.
Every trip out to sea lasts years.
Some die and never come back.
If the three siblings used to work here,
does that mean Anan is involved in this?
Thai fisheries were banned by Europe
due to reports of human trafficking.
The government issued strict regulations.
The Fishery Association
did their best to clean things up.
But Chai is the only one
still getting away with it.
What do you think?
[sentimental ballad
playing over cell phone]
Hello?
Seya.
[in Burmese] Seya, calm down.
Speak slowly. What happened?
[foreboding music playing]
Seya.
I don't know what to do anymore.
- Where did they take my sister?
- Seya, calm down, okay?
- What happened?
- Nay Oo is gone.
[in Thai] Did you find Nay Oo?
I lied.
I brought Nay Oo to hide here.
We were going to run away together.
[sobs] But she disappeared.
It has to be those cops, right?
The ones that came for me.
Calm down.
She might have run away somewhere.
No way.
Our great-grandmother gave us these
when we crossed into Thailand.
She wouldn't leave it behind like this.
[sobbing softly]
If they do something to Nay Oo too…
I'll kill them.
[Seya breathes shakily]
Take it easy, Seya. Calm down.
[music rises]
[music fades]
[Tah over video]
This issue is still trending…
Holy shit. The tables have turned.
[Tah] …about what really happened.
Right now,
I'm sitting with Attorney Manao…
Damn, she looks spicy.
Mek.
- Mek, look at this.
- Give me a sec.
I'm telling you,
you need to see this right now.
Actually, I invited her
to come on the show today,
- but she really isn't ready.
- [Tah] That's understandable.
Look, that's Manao,
the boss's old assistant.
She's Pui's lawyer now.
[Tah] …in some angles…
Anyway, did you watch the last episode?
[Manao] I did.
Did you see that their side insisted
that the doctor didn't do it
and that he's a very good person?
Witnesses filled the whole studio.
As for the 50,000-baht transfer,
it was out of pity
and a genuine desire to help.
They'll do whatever it takes
to make people believe them.
I know exactly what kind of person
their lawyer is.
Huh? You mean Attorney Jittri?
Wow. [clicks tongue]
What does that smirk mean?
Does it mean you believe
they're definitely not telling the truth?
Well, I want everyone
to judge for themselves from this clip.
THE TABLES TURN! DOCTOR IN TROUBLE
THE MOTHER POWER LAWYER REVEALS EVIDENCE
[Pui over video]
I'll press charges against you
for non-consensual sex.
[sniffles]
- [Korn] Listen, how much do you want?
- [ominous music playing]
- Is 20,000 enough?
- [Pui] I don't want your money.
I want justice.
[Korn] Alright, fine.
I'll give you 50,000.
But just once.
Let's consider it a win-win.
Shit, caught red-handed on video.
Dr. Korn is finished.
- Case closed.
- Hold on.
[Tah] I have to ask you,
aren't you afraid they might argue…
They might say she intentionally
filmed this to blackmail the doctor.
If she meant to blackmail,
wouldn't she have spent the money by now?
Here's the evidence.
Dr. Korn transferred 50,000 baht.
Transfer evidence.
A direct slip from Dr. Korn himself.
[Tah] He transferred immediately
and even sent the slip?
[Manao] Yes. As soon as she got the money,
she immediately filed a police report.
[Tah] Well, let me ask. Do you have
any message to send to the other side?
[sighs] I'll see you in court.
[music fades]
[Kung] Manao's upgraded herself.
Now she's as sour as her name.
A full package.
She's getting too good at this.
She wasn't this good when she was with us.
- [Pui] I'll press charges against you…
- [Kung] Ah, found some lime.
- …for non-consensual sex.
- Lime, huh?
Throw out all the lime juice
in the fridge, Nemo.
- Hey.
- [Kung] Yeah?
The wording in the clip is weird.
What is it?
"Charges against you
for non-consensual sex."
It sounds like she memorized it.
Well, maybe Pui knows the law.
People can be educated, you know?
It's possible she knows the law,
but what kind of person
speaks in legal jargon like that?
And her tone sounds totally deliberate.
Tricking the doctor to transfer the money
to use it for the police report.
What if Attorney Manao
was the one who planned for the victim
to entrap Dr. Korn?
- [Kung] Right.
- If the court finds out about this,
this evidence will hold no weight.
[foreboding music playing]
Holy shit.
I've seen the boss use this tactic.
Manao worked here for a long time.
She learned some of Jittri's tactics.
[sniffs, chuckles]
You're pretty sharp, damn it.
The problem is how we can prove it.
[chuckles] Have you heard
of the Pantip Conan?
[dark intriguing music playing]
[Kung] The Mother Power Lawyer.
Manao used to lash out at me all the time.
The clip was filmed on November 30th.
That means Pui
had contacted Manao before that.
- Nemo.
- Yes, sir.
Facebook, IG, X, TikTok.
Search back to November 30th.
- Get on it.
- You got it, boss.
THE MOTHER POWER LAWYER
- [mouse wheel rattling]
- [intense intriguing music playing]
PHYSICAL ABUSE BY A HUSBAND
IS A CRIMINAL OFFENSE
Manao's IG is full of her baby pictures.
She's so obsessed.
Oh, so cute and chubby! So adorable!
What the hell is wrong with you?
Keep searching.
Trying to be the honey
to her lime? Bastard.
INTERNATIONAL DAY FOR THE ELIMINATION
OF VIOLENCE AGAINST WOMEN
[music turns tense]
I NEED ADVICE.
IF I SUSPECT A DOCTOR DID SOMETHING TO ME,
BUT HAVE NO PROOF, WHAT SHOULD I DO?
THE MOTHER POWER LAWYER:
CAN YOU GIVE ME MORE DETAILS?
WHAT HAPPENED AND WHAT KIND OF DOCTOR?
I HAD BACK PAIN,
SO I WENT TO AN ORTHOPEDIC CLINIC.
BUT HE MADE ME TAKE OFF MY SHIRT
AND TOUCHED ME, CLAIMING IT WAS TREATMENT.
THE MOTHER POWER LAWYER:
MAY I DM YOU?
- [mouse clicks]
- [mouse wheel rattles]
- Shit, I think I found it.
- [Kung] Huh?
Where?
You think this is it?
I think it is.
The plot is way too familiar.
Damn. Are you a psychic, Mek?
You've got a damn sixth sense.
Back the fuck off.
Keep your smelly breath away.
Click on her profile.
[mouse clicks]
BLISSIS LOCKED HER PROFILE.
[Mek] All locked up. We can't snoop.
- [chuckles]
- [music concludes]
You know any top-tier internet sleuths?
- [daring music playing]
- [Mek] Damn.
[chuckles] That's not me.
[music concludes]
[Kung] What the hell are the glasses for?
Blocking blue light, bro.
[upbeat electronic music playing]
[mouse clicking]
[keyboard clacking]
PLUS-SIZE WOMEN'S CLOTHING
[mouse clicks]
[mouse wheel rattles]
[keyboard keys clacking]
[keyboard keys clack]
Wait. Look at this for a sec.
This one. Click on this one.
[music concludes]
JUST A REMINDER I GOT THROUGH IT.
BYE, MY FRIEND, BIPOLAR.
[Kung] Holy shit. Bipolar.
[tense music playing]
[mouse clicks]
I CAN'T ESCAPE IT.
WELCOME BACK, MY OLD FRIEND.
RISPERIDONE
PSYCHIATRIC MEDICATION
[Kung] Seems pretty serious.
Should we use this against her?
- Don't do that, man.
- [music fades]
It has nothing to do with the case.
And don't tell this to Jittri.
Hey, I can't do that.
The boss needs to know everything.
It's too sensitive.
Just Pui's posts
talking to Manao are enough.
[bag zipper closes]
Hey.
Damn, you're as kind as Santa Claus.
[Mek] I'm out.
[Nemo] Damn, I wasted all that time
searching for nothing.
No! Don't go out yet.
[tense music playing]
There's a random car parked out front.
I don't know who sent them.
- [Kung] Bro.
- [Nemo] Fuck, who is it?
Mai is blocking them.
I don't know whose car it is.
They've been here a while.
Just parked there, staking us out.
I've got Ek's gang watching them.
[Kung] Damn it.
[Meuk] Headlights are on too.
If the battery dies, don't help them out.
- [Kung] Idiots.
- [Nemo] What's the plan?
I'll handle this.
Hey, fuckers!
[banging on car]
- [Kung] Who the fuck are you?!
- [Meuk] Film them!
- [Kung] Damn it!
- What the fuck?
- [Kung] Get out!
- Get out!
You think I don't know, you bastard?!
Get out!
- [music stops abruptly]
- [insects chirping]
[car door closes]
Why are you here?
Girlfriend?
A relationship
I knew nothing about. [sniffs]
I banged on her car for nothing.
Almost broke my hand, damn it!
[Kung groans]
Boss!
[intriguing musical sting plays]
Nay Oo did sneak over to see Seya.
But the room I saw was completely trashed.
There must have been a struggle.
And there's no way
she ran away on her own
because she promised Seya
they'd go back to Myanmar.
Pang has her team spreading the word now.
If there are any leads on Nay Oo,
they'll contact us right away.
I should've believed you that day.
I'm sorry.
Do you have any information on
who took Nay Oo?
[pensive music playing]
[sighs deeply]
There are no cameras around there.
Nothing at all.
It's a workers' camp.
Pang and I asked everyone,
but nobody saw a thing.
[breathes deeply]
What should we do next?
Since we don't have any leads
on where Nay Oo went,
I still have to keep working on
Dr. Korn's case.
Mek.
What if Nay Oo really was taken
by Anan's men?
Do you think she's still alive?
[music darkens]
[music concludes]
CRIMINAL COURT
WITNESS HEARING: DR. KORN'S CASE
- He's a great doctor.
- I just had my knee surgery.
- I can walk fine now.
- [indistinct chatter]
- [Kung] What did you do? Play soccer?
- [Kanchana] Who would dare do that?
[soft tense music playing]
[Manao] When did you find out
your daughter was violated?
When she started having
chronic back pain last year,
she began taking painkillers every day.
[music concludes]
But it got so bad
that they stopped helping,
so we decided to go see a doctor.
Dr. Korn, the defendant in this case.
[Pui's mother] Yes. It was him.
After we got back from the doctor,
she started acting strangely.
She kept to herself
and wouldn't leave her room.
Until one day,
I heard her crying quietly in her room.
So I kept pressing her,
and she finally told me.
Pui told me that…
on the day she went to the clinic,
the doctor said this kind of pain
could be a uterine tumor.
So he asked to do a pelvic exam.
And then…
he raped her.
[dark, somber music playing]
[exhales deeply]
[inhales sharply]
He told her that…
he's a doctor.
Everybody respects him.
But people like us,
no one would believe a word we say.
[Pui's mother breathes shakily]
Your Honor, please help my daughter.
[Manao] No further questions.
Defense counsel, you may cross-examine.
[music fades]
Were you already aware…
that she returned to the clinic again
after the alleged assault?
Yes.
[Mek] Why did she go back?
She wanted him to take responsibility
for what he did.
Weren't you worried about your daughter
going back to the man
she claims assaulted her?
Please answer the question.
[soft tense music playing]
[Mek] Why did you let her go alone?
Why didn't you go with her?
Or did someone go with her?
She went alone.
I didn't know before she went.
I only found out after she came back.
And before she went,
did she consult anyone?
No.
[Mek] Hmm.
But five days prior,
your daughter posted on
the Mother Power Lawyer page,
and the lawyer replied.
Doesn't that mean
they consulted beforehand?
- Objection.
- [music fades]
The defense is asking
irrelevant questions.
I'm warning the defense counsel.
Please stay on topic.
I'm afraid it is highly relevant.
Because there is a possibility
that your daughter
went back to the clinic
under the lawyer's orders
to fabricate evidence against my client.
[tense music resumes]
Per the supplementary evidence submitted.
Attorney Manao used
her personal social media
to contact your daughter.
Five days later,
your daughter filed a police report
with proof of the money transfer, WJ.5,
and the video evidence of her talking
to the doctor, WJ.3.
The crucial question is this.
Do you think your daughter acted alone,
or followed her lawyer's orders?
You're jumping to conclusions
and accusing me!
Do you have evidence that I advised
the plaintiff to fabricate evidence?
[judge] I am warning you again, Counselor.
Stick to the issues relevant to the case.
Do not make accusations
against the plaintiff's counsel.
[music intensifies]
[music builds]
[music falls]
Let's talk about the medicine.
[music rises]
Regarding the medication
your daughter takes regularly,
is there any other medicine she takes
besides painkillers?
She used to,
but she stopped a long time ago.
An anti-anxiety drug called Risperidone?
What does that have to do with this?
[music concludes]
It's for bipolar disorder, isn't it?
- [crowd murmuring]
- [tense music playing]
Please answer the question.
But my daughter has recovered
and she's been well.
How can you be certain
your daughter won't relapse?
Hold on. You didn't submit this
to the court beforehand.
And this is medical information
you shouldn't be disclosing
without her consent.
How did you find out about this?
Or is this inadmissible evidence?
Ms. Pui posted it on her own social media.
It's public information
that she willingly disclosed.
No further questions.
[music concludes]
[chair scrapes]
[judge] The court will now proceed
with a closed hearing.
Anyone not involved in this case
must leave the courtroom.
As the questioning
will involve sensitive matters,
your cooperation is requested.
[soft dramatic music playing]
[judge] The plaintiff may now enter.
[door creaks]
[gate door opens, closes]
[judge] Counsel for the plaintiff
may proceed.
[music concludes]
Are you ready?
Could you tell us what happened
on the day of the incident?
Just share what you can.
And if you need a break, just let me know.
[hesitates]
I went to the doctor because my back hurt.
And after the initial examination,
he said I might need to be checked
for uterine fibroids.
[somber music playing]
So he told me to take off my pants
and lie on the bed.
Was anyone else in the room at the time?
[inhales deeply] No.
He told the nurse to step out
and manage the patient queue.
[Manao] So during the examination,
there was no third party in the room.
Is that correct?
Correct. It was just me and the doctor.
And I thought that was normal.
He started rubbing my lower abdomen.
[breathes shakily]
[inhales, hesitates]
Then he slowly moved his hand lower.
It hurt.
So I told him to stop.
But he didn't.
He brought his face really close to mine.
And… [sniffles] …he told me…
[breathes shakily]
…"It's okay. This is normal."
What happened after that?
Did he use his hand?
Do not lead the witness, Counselor.
Did he show any particular
expressions or gestures?
I was too scared to look.
I felt…
air blowing…
down…
down there.
And then…
I felt something go inside me.
It hurt so much.
[music darkens]
I was in pain,
but I put up with it because…
I really didn't know what he was doing.
I didn't.
[Pui sobs, sniffles]
Are you okay?
[Pui sobbing]
[inhales deeply]
I couldn't see anything at all,
except the light shining in my face.
I tried to push myself up…
[whimpers]
…but he grabbed my legs and lifted them,
pushing my knees almost to my chest.
[sobbing]
Couldn't you resist at all?
My body just froze.
I could only lie still, and…
I told myself it would be over soon.
[Pui sobs, sniffles]
[music concludes]
[sighs deeply]
No further questions.
The defense may cross-examine.
[tense music playing]
Did you take your bipolar medication
or painkillers before seeing the doctor?
- No.
- Which one didn't you take?
Your mother said
you take painkillers every day.
- I didn't take the bipolar meds.
- [Jittri] Why not?
Taking them together makes me exhausted.
I can't function.
So it affects your daily life.
Meaning when your back hurt,
you only took painkillers
and skipped the bipolar meds?
Objection. Irrelevant.
Let's stick to what's relevant, then.
Did the doctor's hand go in deep?
[music intensifies]
Please answer the question.
I don't know.
Did his fingers enter your vagina first?
- [breathes shakily]
- [Jittri] Answer yes or no.
I don't know.
Did you see the doctor
violate you until he climaxed?
Did he ejaculate?
I don't know.
[Pui sobs, breathes shakily]
And did you climax? Were you satisfied?
- [sobs]
- [Jittri] How did it feel?
How did you feel?
- Could you describe it for us?
- Stop talking!
Your Honor, the defense
is badgering the witness.
Could we call for a recess?
Some bipolar patients suffer
from delusions and hallucinations,
especially during severe episodes.
If they aren't taking their medication,
it's possible
the witness hallucinated the rape,
while the doctor just conducted
a standard examination.
You're not a doctor.
You can't just make random diagnoses!
[judge] Counsel for the defense,
if you continue this,
I will terminate the cross-examination.
Understood.
One last question, then.
So it is possible that on that day,
you were confused
due to not taking medication,
and it led to you
entirely fabricating this rape,
while the doctor did nothing to you,
correct?
- [sobbing]
- [music builds]
[Pui sobbing, muttering]
No further questions.
[Pui sobbing]
[music intensifies]
[music concludes]
[water stops running]
[paper towels rustling]
[breathes shakily]
[Pui sobbing] I can't do this anymore.
[Pui sobs]
I don't want to fight anymore.
You never change.
This is a rape case.
You know what the victim went through.
What you did was like violating her
all over again.
So what should I have done?
Plotted behind their backs?
Secretly filmed the doctor wiring money
to get evidence?
[tense music playing]
[Jittri] It's funny.
You hate me and insult me,
but you use the same methods.
You're good at this, I won't deny that.
But you know deep down how disgusting
it is to hurt a woman like that.
You may not have a child,
but did you ever think,
if you went through what she did,
how your mother would feel?
[music fades]
Insult me all you want.
Play the "Mother Power" card all you want,
I don't care.
But if you ever mention my mother again…
[ominous music playing]
I'll do everything I can to make sure
you have no place in this field
or in society.
If you ever tell my people
to keep secrets from me again,
I'll be the one
who sends you back to prison.
Remember that.
[music concludes]
[reporter] He's not ready
to give an interview.
- However, Mr. Kraiwut Sunthonsahaphop…
- [knocking on door]
…the opposition party leader
- [banging on door]
- …and chairman
believes this issue
needs to be monitored closely.
- [reporter stops]
- [banging on door]
[banging on door]
[gun clicks]
[Chanon sighs]
Why are you knocking-- [yelps]
Hey!
- [Jittri kissing]
- [intense music playing]
[bag thuds]
[bel buckle rattling]
[breathing heavily]
[Jittri moans, pants]
Wait. Hold on.
- [Chanon gasps]
- [Jittri grunts]
- [music builds]
- [Chanon] Stop. Calm down.
- [music concludes]
- What's wrong?
- [Jittri panting]
- [man] Take it easy. Wanna talk about it?
[Jittri breathes shakily]
[pensive music playing]
[pants] I didn't come here to talk.
The doctor's case, right?
And who says Attorney Jittri
doesn't have a soft side?
The guilt doesn't just go away easily…
not until we pay the price.
[door opens]
[door slams shut]
[music fades]
[reporter] …must take responsibility,
and be brought to justice.
Moving on to the case of Dr. Korn,
also known as The Angel's Touch.
He was previously facing
sexual assault charges.
However, the victim
has now dropped the charges
after only a single hearing.
See? The boss is ruthless.
Job done. Mission complete. See?
[in English] Congratulations.
[reporter speaking indistinctly over TV]
[in Thai] What gives?
Was my English not clear?
[reporter] Dr. Korn has now announced
that he will countersue the victim
for 10 million baht
in damages for defamation.
Meanwhile, Attorney Manao
from the Mother Power Law page,
the victim's lawyer,
has come forward to clarify
the reason for dropping the case.
[Manao over TV] I was who advised her
to drop the charges,
because my client's mental state has
severely deteriorated since the hearing.
But I must insist that dropping this case
does not mean Dr. Korn is innocent.
Mek, I went to the flea market.
I saw pennywort juice
and brought you some.
Drink up. It'll help.
Hmm. Help with what?
You really don't know
what you're in for, do you?
In for what?
[downbeat quirky music playing]
Nemo, I said hold him down!
Hold his wrist tightly!
Nemo, hold him down tight.
Look how Meuk's doing it.
Hold him down tight!
[in English] Yo, yo, yo, bro.
I got you, bro.
I love you, bro. You can do it, bro.
[in Thai] You can totally take it.
You're my tough guy.
[breathes shakily]
Uh, Doc… It won't hurt too much, right?
- [music concludes]
- Or would you rather go to jail?
- Right here, Doctor.
- [Korn] Hmm.
[in singsong] Just a little pinch!
Just a little pinch!
Just a little scratch, right, Doc?
[giggles]
[Korn] Hmm…
- Ready?
- [music resumes]
Just a sec.
Come here.
[breathes shakily]
- [music concludes]
- [Nemo in English] I got you.
- [mallet thuds]
- [Mek screams]
[music resumes]
DR. KORN SOPHONCHITRAK
[music concludes]
[reporter in Thai]
Moving on to our next story.
This case has certainly become
the talk of the town.
The Golf Course Murder case.
It's a name many of you
are very familiar with.
For the latest update on this case,
the court has scheduled the next hearing
for two weeks from now.
Mr. Mek continues to deny
all charges against him.
Our news team
will continue to follow the hearing…
[suspenseful music playing]
[switch clicks]
[light buzzing faintly]
[plastic rustling]
[dark intriguing music playing]
[music continues, intensifies]
[dark tense music playing]
[music concludes]